export let questions = [{
    "question": "What is Luke Skywalker’s wife Mara’s last name?",
    "options": ["Ruby", "Jade", "Garnet"],
    "answer": "Jade"
}, {
    "question": "Tenel Ka Djo is princess and eventually queen of what planet?",
    "options": ["Hapes", "Dathomir", "Yavin IV"],
    "answer": "Hapes"
}, {
    "question": "Timothy Zahn’s trilogy of novels that were credited with reigniting interest in the Star Wars Expanded Universe are called the ______ Trilogy.",
    "options": ["Vader", "Pellaeon", "Thrawn"],
    "answer": "Thrawn"
}, {
    "question": "What is Jacen Solo's Sith name?",
    "options": ["Darth Bane", "Darth Caedus", "Darth Sidious"],
    "answer": "Darth Caedus"
}, {
    "question": "Which of the Solo children does Chewbacca save before being killed?",
    "options": ["Jaina", "Anakin", "Jacen"],
    "answer": "Anakin"
}, {
    "question": "In 'The Lando Calrissian Adventures', what is the name of Lando’s droid companion?",
    "options": ["Vuffi Raa", "Em Teedee", "Thon Baka"],
    "answer": "Vuffi Raa"
}, {
    "question": "What are the Yuuzhan Vong’s ships made of?",
    "options": ["stone", "metal", "coral"],
    "answer": "coral"
}, {
    "question": "In ‘The Truce at Bakura’, who is arrested for sedition?",
    "options": ["Leia", "Luke", "Han"],
    "answer": "Leia"
}, {
    "question": "Who is one of Leia’s closest friends, and caretaker of her children?",
    "options": ["Winter", "Autumn", "Summer"],
    "answer": "Winter"
}, {
    "question": "Who does Jaina Solo marry?",
    "options": ["Zekk", "Kyp Durron", "Jagged Fel"],
    "answer": "Jagged Fel"
}, {
    "question": "In the Star Wars universe, GFFA stands for the Galactic Federation of _____ Alliances.",
    "options": ["Force", "Free", "Former"],
    "answer": "Free"
}, {
    "question": "How do Leia's noghri bodyguards address her?",
    "options": ["Lady Organa", "Lady Solo", "Lady Vader"],
    "answer": "Lady Vader"
}, {
    "question": "What is Leia's role in the New Republic?",
    "options": ["Chief of State", "Jedi Knight", "General"],
    "answer": "Chief of State"
}, {
    "question": "What superweapon did Kyp Durron steal?",
    "options": ["Planet Killer", "Sun Crusher", "Death Star III"],
    "answer": "Sun Crusher"
}, {
    "question": "Cloud City has never been used as a ________.",
    "options": ["gas mine", "zoo", "casino"],
    "answer": "zoo"
}, {
    "question": "Jaina Solo has the title _______ of the Jedi bestowed up on her.",
    "options": ["queen", "leader", "sword"],
    "answer": "sword"
}, {
    "question": "Who is Allana Solo's father?",
    "options": ["Jacen Solo", "Han Solo", "Anakin Solo"],
    "answer": "Jacen Solo"
}, {
    "question": "Where is Wedge Antilles from?",
    "options": ["Corellia", "Coruscant", "Tatooine"],
    "answer": "Corellia"
}, {
    "question": "What was Tycho Celchu's main role in the Rebel Alliance?",
    "options": ["soldier", "pilot", "cook"],
    "answer": "pilot"
}, {
    "question": "What is Ord Mantell known for?",
    "options": ["smugglers", "gemstones", "rain"],
    "answer": "smugglers"
}];